Wait a minute!
Then then...
What about plan C?
Uhh... what happened to plan B again?
Ah well, whatever.
Now, now, this should be fine first, right?
Before you attack me, I’m gonna let
you in on some classified information.
And you all will change your minds.
Just like a mountain’s weather!
Illia, Ricardo. Got your bullets ready?
Locked and loaded.
Naturally!
Don’t shoot at someone defenseless!
Wait, hear me out!!
I’ll spill the beans now! Okay?
Now, boy?
Lend me your ear for a bit.
I’ll pay you back later.
Huh? Me?
Ruca!
Don’t listen to this guy!
Now, now, boy.
Listen closely...
This is the sound of a blade tearing through flesh...
Crap!!
YOU BASTARD!!
Ruca, hang in there!!