I had a dream
In a faraway place
In a faraway land
There, I--
Why am I in this world!
Right now, at this time, at this place!
Why was I born!?
And what meaning does that reason hold!?
The answer to that is in this battle!!
To unify the two realms!
From this day forth, we are no longer rebels.
All of Cielo and the future generations
Will know us as Sensus!
And soon, we shall obtain the Manifest: the Eternal Wish!
And grant us our ideal world!
ALL TROOPS! CHARGE!
Asura, take care...
Lord Asura...
Lady Inanna, Lady Sakuya.
If it's Lord Asura, then he will surely
do a splendid job conquering that fortress.
Hahahaha!!
Dear mother, the battle will get boring if you don't hold backï¼
If this battle is boring,
Then how about you let me make it more interesting.
However, you'll have to pay with your life!
Reaper Hypnos... is that what they call you?
I take it your brother is in good health?
Do not mention my brother...
Shut up and let yourself be killed by my hand.
Have you grown tired of stealing souls from
Terro that you've come to steal mine instead?
I'm surprised you were able to break
through the barrier laid by the Senate.
As expected of the Rebels' commander.
"Rebel" you say...?
I am tired of hearing that name.
If you're tired of it, then what shall I call you?
Our name is "Sensus"!
I shall carve it upon your body so you will not forget!
With this holy sword Durandal!
Interesting! Then let us battle!
Not yet... I'm not dead yet...
Without me to gather souls from Terro,
Cielo will...
Our ideal... once Terro's united with Cielo
there is no more need to worry.
Rest yourself and witness this world's future!
...So be it.
From the day I reincarnate once again...
I shall find out from you... the outcome!
Behold! Hypnos of Ratio has fallen!
Forward, Sensus!
From this point on, the Celestial Castle is ours!
And we will obtain the Manifest...
And fulfill our ideals!
And soon... soon...
The wish of the Primordial Giant...
and our goal...
As long as I obtain it... yes...
as long as I have it...